<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<content xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="content.xsd">
  <apptitle>LosViajesdeMaura</apptitle>
  <appintro><![CDATA[A Bolivian <strong>Traveler</strong> ,  <strong>Blogger</strong> &amp; <strong>Dreamer</strong> ]]></appintro>
  <article id="1">
    <title>Japan and the mystery of their Geishas</title>
    <date>June 2018</date>
    <image>/images/P1040121.JPG</image>
    <body><![CDATA[<p>Beyond the temples, the millenary culture and the many traditions, Japan is a country of mysteries 
        and the Geishas are one of those well-kept secrets that everyone speaks and few know. We will walk through 
        the narrow streets of Kyoto and enter the mystical world of these muses of Japanese art and culture.</p>]]>
    </body>
  </article>
  <article id="2">
    <title>Thailand among their temples, smiling people, massages and street food.</title>
    <date>January 2019</date>
    <image>/images/Thailand1.JPG</image>
    <body><![CDATA[
            <p>Thailand is a Southeast Asian country. It's known for tropical beaches, opulent royal palaces, 
                ancient ruins and ornate temples displaying figures of Buddha. In Bangkok, the capital, an ultramodern 
                cityscape rises next to quiet canalside communities and the iconic temples of Wat Arun, Wat Pho and the 
                Emerald Buddha Temple (Wat Phra Kaew).</p>]]></body>
  </article>
  <article id="3">
    <title>The 'Big Five' diamonds of South Africa</title>
    <date>September 2019</date>
    <image>/images/P1110590.JPG</image>
    <body><![CDATA[<p>South Africa is a diverse country with incredible landscapes, rich culture and a hard history in terms 
        of the struggle for equality and freedom of its inhabitants. Without a doubt, the &#39;cherry cake&#39; or the most 
        attractive thing in South Africa is the experience of making a safari and having the privilege of meeting the &#39;Big 
        Five&#39; that are the Lion, the elephant, the leopard, the rhino and the buffalo.</p>]]></body>
  </article>
  <product id="1">
    <title><![CDATA[
        <h5>Travel Essentials kit </h5>
        <p>Medium compact biodegradable plastic bag, useful for carrying basic personal hygiene products. </p> ]]>
    </title>
    <image>/images/Product-1.jpg</image>
    <price>30.00</price>
  </product>
  <product id="2">
    <title><![CDATA[
        <h5>Travel Power Adapter </h5>
        <p>2 x UK to EU Europe European Travel Adapter suitable for France, Germany, Spain, Egypt, China.</p> ]]>
    </title>
    <image>/images/Product-2.jpg</image>
    <price>15.00</price>
  </product>
  <product id="3">
    <title><![CDATA[
        <h5>Backpack</h5>
        <p>Sports 40L Lightweight Packable Backpack, durable water resistant, really recommend for travel hiking 
        and camping outdoor. travel hiking and camping outdoor. Foldable daypack for women and men </p> ]]>
    </title>
    <image>/images/Backpack1.jpg</image>
    <price>50.00</price>
  </product>
  <product id="4">
    <title><![CDATA[
        <h5>Travel Makeup Kit </h5>
        <p>Cosmetic Travel Bag Waterproof Makeup Brush Toiletry Organiser for men and women Black.</p> ]]>
    </title>
    <image>/images/Product-4.jpg</image>
    <price>25.00</price>
  </product>
  <product id="5">
    <title><![CDATA[
        <h5>Travel Neck Pillow </h5>
        <p>Purefly Travel Pillow, luxuriously, soft, inflatable neck pillow support-compact and lightweight for sleeping 
        on airplane, car and train, carrying bag soft and ergonomic</p> ]]>
    </title>
    <image>/images/Product-5.jpg</image>
    <price>14.99</price>
  </product>
</content>